

CONTACT

- No. 21, Anura Mawatha,
 Borupana Road, Ratmalana
- . 0716101051
- 🛪 sachitha.dharshana@gmail.com
- in https://bit.ly/3frcMpd

SKILLS

Front End languages: HTML, CSS & JavaScript

Frameworks and Libraries: Bootstrap, Material UI and WordPress

Databases: MySQL

Hands on Experience in: React JS

REFEREES

Mr. Saminda Premaratne Head

Department of Information
Technology Faculty of Information
Technology University of Moratuwa

Tel: 0714413362

Tel: 0117544801

Mr. Samantha Rajapakse Senior Lecturer SLIIT, New Kandy Rd, Malabe

SACHITHA DHARSHANA KAHAKACHCHI

Frontend Developer

I'm Sachitha, a 25 year old outgoing individual with strong design and development problem solving skills. Expert in HTML, CSS, JS, PHP and WordPress. Strong knowledge on web coding standards and best practices. Skilled in providing requirement specifications, user documentation etc. Fluent in English with strong written and verbal skills. As a fast learner, I bring energy and enthusiasm with great interpersonal and team player skills. I value work ethic and working in a multi-cultural environment for my career progress.

JOB EXPERIENCE

Webmaster

Bizycorp Pvt. Ltd

NOV 2018 - PRESENT

Offering total website solutions & SEO services for Doctors to dominate search engine rankings. Specialized in Digital Marketing Agency that deliver results. Dedicated to help your business grow online with SEO, PPC etc. My roles and responsibilities were:

- Developing & re-designing new client websites and upgrading (conversion) existing sites keeping in line with new technologies
- Attending to internal meetings
- Research and Learning

Web Developer

Fiverr

JAN 2020 - PRESENT

Provided freelancing services to create WordPress websites for clients and optimize performance of existing client websites as per Google PageSpeed insights and GTMetrix. I was involved in the following:

- Design and develop WordPress websites.
- Optimize performance and improve loading time for existing client websites
- Graphic design Adobe photoshop and Adobe illustrator

Web developer LivingDreams Pvt. Ltd FEB 2017 - JAN 2018

Living Dreams Web Development Solutions; A Sydney based Web Development company that offers Web Development, Web Design and Ecommerce Solutions. Involved in the following:

- Deep expertise and hands on experience with web programming languages such as HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and WordPress
- Team work and client liaison
- Testing and debugging

EDUCATION

Master of Science in Information Technology (Reading) University Of Moratuwa 2020 - 2022

Bachelor of Science Degree in Information Technology Sri Lankan Institute of Information Technology (SLIIT) 2015 - 2017